{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Chimney \u0026 Fireplace Cleaning Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40034/":{"taskOID":40034,"originalTaskOID":40034,"setID":358,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5507,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Services","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What services do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1379,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Chimney sweeping","answerDisplayText":"Chimney sweeping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1377,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Chimney inspection","answerDisplayText":"Chimney inspection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3246,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install chimney cap","answerDisplayText":"Install chimney cap","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6921,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Waterproofing","answerDisplayText":"Waterproofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500642,"questionDisplayText":"How many chimney flues need cleaning?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many chimney flues need cleaning?","shortQuestionText":"How many chimney flues need cleaning?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1209,"questionDisplayText":"Burning Device/Fireplace","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of fireplace or burning device do you use?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6459,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Traditional masonry fireplace (brick or stone)","answerDisplayText":"Traditional masonry fireplace (brick or stone)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7092,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood stove","answerDisplayText":"Wood stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4635,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pellet stove","answerDisplayText":"Pellet stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2750,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Gas fireplace insert","answerDisplayText":"Gas fireplace insert","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4876,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Prefabricated fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Prefabricated fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5507,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Services","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What services do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1379,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Chimney sweeping","answerDisplayText":"Chimney sweeping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1377,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Chimney inspection","answerDisplayText":"Chimney inspection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3246,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install chimney cap","answerDisplayText":"Install chimney cap","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6921,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Waterproofing","answerDisplayText":"Waterproofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1379,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Chimney sweeping","answerDisplayText":"Chimney sweeping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1377,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Chimney inspection","answerDisplayText":"Chimney inspection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3246,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install chimney cap","answerDisplayText":"Install chimney cap","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6921,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Waterproofing","answerDisplayText":"Waterproofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500642,"questionDisplayText":"How many chimney flues need cleaning?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many chimney flues need cleaning?","shortQuestionText":"How many chimney flues need cleaning?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1209,"questionDisplayText":"Burning Device/Fireplace","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of fireplace or burning device do you use?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6459,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Traditional masonry fireplace (brick or stone)","answerDisplayText":"Traditional masonry fireplace (brick or stone)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7092,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood stove","answerDisplayText":"Wood stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4635,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pellet stove","answerDisplayText":"Pellet stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2750,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Gas fireplace insert","answerDisplayText":"Gas fireplace insert","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4876,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Prefabricated fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Prefabricated fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6459,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Traditional masonry fireplace (brick or stone)","answerDisplayText":"Traditional masonry fireplace (brick or stone)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7092,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood stove","answerDisplayText":"Wood stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4635,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pellet stove","answerDisplayText":"Pellet stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2750,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Gas fireplace insert","answerDisplayText":"Gas fireplace insert","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4876,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Prefabricated fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Prefabricated fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40034/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40034,"taskName":"Chimney or Fireplace - Clean and Inspect","taskDescription":"Clean and Inspect a Chimney or Fireplace","xmTaskDescriptor":"Chimney \u0026 Fireplace Cleaning Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":43,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"chimney inspect sweep fireplace clean","textMessagingName":"Clean Fireplace","rolloverLongDesc":"Cleans soot \u0026 creosote from the inside of the chimney as well as the fireplace.  Also inspect for damage \u0026 any potential hazards. Often clean heating flues at the same time. Some even clean dryer vents.","rolloverShortDesc":"Chimney sweep cleans soot \u0026 creosote from inside chimney.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Clean and Inspect a Chimney or Fireplace.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e Chimney Cleaners | \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e Fireplace Cleaning","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":13,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Clean \u0026 Inspect Chimney","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Chimney or Fireplace - Clean and Inspect","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Chimney \u0026 Fireplace Cleaning Project","urlName":"Chimney-or-Fireplace-Clean-and-Inspect","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Chimney Sweeps \u0026 Cleaners - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"chimney, inspect, sweep, fireplace, clean, soot, cap, lining, fire, place","emcCategoryOid":-12014,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":358,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}